(Penny:)Well, remember Kurt?
(Leonard:)Your ex-boyfriend?
(Penny:)Yeah, he got arrested
for taking a whiz on a cop car.
- What?
- He was drunk.
(Leonard:)I would hope so.
(Penny:)He had a bunch of outstanding tickets
and a bench warrant, so I...
(Penny:)You know, I paid his fines.
(Leonard:)Did he pay you back?
(Penny:)No, but he will.
(Leonard:)And that's based
on the inherent credit-worthiness...
(Leonard:)...of people who get drunk
and urinate on police vehicles?
(Penny:)Leonard, I'm not gonna call up Kurt
and ask him for money.
Oh?
(Leonard:)What are you gonna do?
I don't know but I might have to find
a cheaper place to live.
(Penny:)Oh, no.
No, you don't wanna do that.
(Penny:)Why not?
Uh, moving is a big deal.
Uh, you... You have to go
to the supermarket and get boxes...
(Leonard:)...and if they're not clean
then your books smell like melons and it's...
(Leonard:)Why don't you just get a roommate
and stay here?